(Penny:)What did I do? Hung upside down
from the monkey bars...
(Penny:)...let all the boys see my underpants.
You can't blame yourseIf.
(Amy:)When your pre-frontal cortex fails
to make you happy...
(Amy:)...promiscuity rewards you
with dopamine.
(Amy:)We neurobiologists refer to this
as the skank reflex.
- You know what? Let's get out of here.
- Where are we going?
(Penny:)Somewhere
where no one's seen me naked.
We may have to drive a while.
(Sheldon:)Subtlety isn't her strong suit, is it?
Oh, can I stay at your place
for a few nights?
Really? A best-friend sleepover? Yay.
Yeah, sure. Yay, heh.
(Amy:)We'll make popcorn, stay up all night,
and I'll teach you my secret language.
- Sounds great.
- Nope. Sounds: